I put a yellow and a black tape on it
Ahhh!
I'm sorry.
There you go.
The terrace?
It's private.
It's part of the apartment.
It's registered as a disaster.
Okay.
What is it?
Can you hear me?
No, I can't hear anything.
Yes, absolutely.
And we're at the heart of the wedding.
In the middle of an animation district.
This kind of apartment
is hard to find in Paris.
The owners of this apartment
don't put it on the market.
The walls are very...
dark.
The owner is a bit like a chipot
when the last locator left
she asked him to repaint
two months ago.
He said he needed to repaint
but not of any color.
So, to avenge
he repainted it in black.
But it's a bit too much.
Because it's in some places
the blackness is perfect
as...
Attention.
What is your son's name?
Alphonse.
Be careful because the floor is very slippery.
What is the concept of the columns
in the middle of the room?
It's feng shui.
Yes, feng shui.
The owner wanted to create a flow of energy
between the living room
and the bedroom.
Alphonse.
Alphonse!
Sir, you asked me to stay calm.
Alphonse.
I'm really angry.
He's adopted.
Why do you say that?
Sir, you're an immobilized agent.
We visit an apartment.
It's not a family therapy.
It's not serious at all.
What is that?
What is it?
And when we know what it is,
we'll call again.
It's not a problem.
Madam.
Sorry.
I have to answer you.
It's my parents.
Yes, dad.
You're my client.
I can...
Huh?
What?
What's that?
Okay.
I have to read you the whole test.
Can you read it?
According to the law,
I'm supposed to read the whole test.
Can you read the whole test?
It's not serious.
You listened to your mother's test.
It takes time.
Philip, I'm 50 years old.
My mother is dead.
I'm not hungry.
Take this round.
The food is delicious.
It's the Belgian chocolate.
As much as the wine is disgusting,
it doesn't taste like chocolate.
I don't know how they do it.
Philip, are you going to please us?
It won't be that complicated.
My mother had nothing.
Nothing?
You don't have a car.
No value items.
That's enough.
My mother wasn't crazy about you.
So we read this nothing.
We sign where you tell us.
And we go to the next stage.
In fact,
it's not exactly like that.
Yes, what?
Your mother owned a furniture store in Paris.
Which one?
A furniture store in the 19th century.
Can you tell me what you find funny?
What I find funny is that
imagine that your wife bought a furniture store
and you weren't running.
I'm not sure she bought it.
She found it in the street?
Why didn't you tell us before?
It's a professional secret, Olivier.
I'm your best friend.
I know, but your mother didn't tell me anything.
So she found it in the street?
Wait, please.
Dad, I need to understand
what's going on.
What's going on?
Your mother owned this furniture store.
She liked it.
It's supposed to be good news.
Good news, good news.
And if not, your wife is crying.
She owns her wedding box collection.
Can you still use it?
Do we exchange it?
There are localities in this furniture store.
All apartments are empty.
Except one.
There's a locality.
Her name is Liliane Petresco.
She pays 550 euros per month.
No, but it must be a knowledge of your mother.
If I were you,
I'd give her her share
and I'd sell the whole furniture store.
Olivier?
Yes.
Olivier,
my condolences.
Can you move your car, please?
Yes, in five minutes.
What's that?
Nothing.
It's for the clients. I just tasted it.
Taste it?
Enjoy it.
I'm tired of doing this kind of thing.
This thing,
a lot of shit,
it's going to be different before bed.
It's a combination of authentic scarves.
Yes, I don't care, Philippe.
You remind me of my mother.
You free us.
We sign here.
No, don't worry.
If you want, we can go together.
Yes.
Come on.
See you there at three o'clock, okay?
Anyway, Julia's going to throw the trash.
Say goodbye.
Come on, Julia.
It's funny.
You're going to throw the trash away?
Why?
It's a women's world.
We don't have time to waste.
You don't want us to stop?
And then I'll make you some courses?
I'll take away friends.
But you don't want me to bring you home?
I'm going to take a beer
and then I'll find a place to sleep.
Come on.
Wait, I have something for you.
What?
A cognac bottle?
A company animal?
You remember what the doctor said, right?
On balance.
It's an idiot.
No, listen.
I'm going to let you fall.
You're going to break your neck.
Okay.
I'm going to do what the idiot said.
Bob, I data well.
I'm going to dig.
It's an idiot, isn't it Bob?
You can't be each other's computer.
It's cool.
No problem.
No problem?
How is that educational?
School double.
This is the number 27 of the future of General Brunet.
There's no number on the buildings.
The 27?
Yes.
Yes, that's me.
Okay, thank you. Good continuation.
Yes, look, I am General Brunet.
Number 27.
Yes, all the way down there.
You have the first floor.
If you go up a little bit here, you have terraces.
And there you even have the lippards for the guy who lives in his penthouse.
Did you find it on the plate?
On the plate?
One day, I was cleaning under the building.
And it fell on my head.
Okay, I immediately saw that you were a kind of distinguished guy.
Yes.
Would you give me 20 euros?
What?
Would you give me 20 euros for me?
My mother has a cancer from pancreas.
If you give me 20 euros, I could pay her a hot drink.
I don't have the money.
Are you kidding me?
It's true, but it's time to start, sir.
I'm not kidding.
My mother is really sick.
So if you give me 10 euros, I could pay her a bowl of soup.
And tell me, she's in a bad mood.
It's the shit of your mother.
Hey, it's 5 euros.
No, I don't have it.
I don't give a shit, but at least you believe me.
Hey!
Hey, stop it!
Shut up!
Oh, fuck!
Shit!
Are you all right?
Well, I had a good time in New York.
Really?
What's that?
That?
Yes.
It's for the baby.
Ah!
Next to the shoe store, there's an animal.
When I went out, I saw this fish that was swimming.
He was looking at me.
We don't swim, fish.
You see what I mean?
It's a very rare species.
What?
Do you know the story of the fish that makes them want to?
The salesman of the store told me that in the original account,
it was exactly this species.
If you choose me, it's for happiness.
But I'm your fish.
Yes, yes.
Tell me just a second.
No, but...
Be careful, he's fragile.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
You're stupid!
Wait, are you all right?
I'm just kidding.
There's always no confidence with you.
No, but...
Don't worry, it's not your baby yet.
It's just a stupid fish.
It doesn't look like a stupid fish.
Are you all right?
Yes.
You don't have to be so stressed out.
I'm going to sell him the fact that
it's not a place worthy of a woman of her age,
but because she was a friend of your mother.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
You want to find a more suitable place.
It's not suitable for you.
You saw yourself, you're red like a tomato.
You know,
when I think I'm going to become a father,
what scares me the most is that my child runs away.
And I don't have the strength to follow him.
Well, for the first year, they're going to be cramped.
So you can only be cramped behind her.
Listen,
I forgot to tell you.
I'll be back in the corner tomorrow.
I have an appointment with your office.
For what?
I told you, I have to have some money.
I don't have money, so I can't do that at home.
But if I do, when he comes, what do I do?
Well, you'll have the chance to meet him.
He's an immobilized promoter,
a superman type.
I already talked about your imbecile, by the way.
He's a potential buyer.
You know I'd rather you ask me for my opinion,
before I propose my own good to people you owe money to.
How many floors are there?
We are.
Come on, do your job.
I can do what I can.
Who the hell is he, Franτois?
He's old. He's probably dead.
You say that for such a long time?
Yes.
Do you remember?
You've got it.
It's like you were in love.
Nobody's at home.
Shit.
Are we going to eat a piece?
No way. If I'm late, Julia's going to make me a scene.
She's jealous.
Charlotte was like that too. She always thought I was wrong.
No way.
Tronie immobilized, hello.
No, it's nothing new.
It's four bedrooms, the roof is locked.
It's perfect.
Very good.
Olivier, there's an elevator.
What can I tell you, Mr Jardin?
Mr Jardin?
I think he's an expert in Paris.
No, I think he's an expert in Paris. This apartment is a mess.
Ah!
Are you okay? Everything's fine?
Yes.
Excuse me.
When you arrived near the elevator, what did you see?
That is to say that Philippe didn't move.
The fish was moving without stopping.
He looked at me.
The fish looked at you.
It's a very special fish.
The Chinese say it exudes the...
The Chinese...
And when Philippe showed me the first time, I got mad at him.
He was ugly.
The fish?
His daughter must have been happy the other day.
He wanted to offer him something special.
Who? Philippe?
Is that the name of the fish?
48 minutes.
You think so?
Yes, I said so.
I said, ma'am, I lost my voice.
Yes, I said ma'am or doctor.
I may be a little doctor, but what does it change?
What does it matter?
You're not going to start again?
Wait, wait.
Listen to me.
I'm here to get rid of this fucking knife that you put in my skin.
I'm not going to the hospitals to find fucking shots.
No, no, I'm not going to kill you.
It's not against you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But, but yes, I may be smiling.
I'm smiling because of politeness, but it's not like with your sister.
With your sister, I was drunk.
Hello?
We're going to pick them up.
Don't you see the fire?
Thank you.
What happened to you?
I saved the life of a friend.
A friend?
It's a friend, yes.
The car that was turned upside down, then it took fire.
The windows were completely closed.
They started to convulcate inside.
So I...
I knew what I was doing, I knew what I was doing, but...
Until life broke apart.
And life broke apart.
And I thought my arm was broken.
What did you do?
I did what anyone would do to my place.
Anyone? Like a hero?
I wish I had a friend like you.
Hello, you're welcome on Julia's local message.
You can leave me a message after the beep.
Good evening, Julia.
What's up?
I'm in a hurry.
I don't want to talk to Julia anymore.
I can't sleep this night. I hug you so hard. Goodbye.
That's why.
We're the Jordanians.
Well, I'm a troddy.
What's going on?
We're not used to having visits with an immobilized agent in Chaucette.
Oh, the Jordanians. I'm sorry.
I just got out of the hospital.
I had a chronic trauma that affected my memory in the short term.
But now, it's much better, Souda.
The mission, Madame Jordan.
How could I forget?
Come in.
We can visit this apartment.
You came for this.
Can you hear me?
No, I can't hear you.
The terrace is private.
No, it's not.
The bedroom is empty.
Come and see if we'd like to show you something.
This is humidity, isn't it?
Mr. Tronnier, the ceiling has humidity.
So?
It shouldn't be like that.
There are many things in this world that shouldn't be like that, Madame Jordan.
And yet, they're coming.
The families of Darfur, the massacres in Syria.
A child who's being crushed on the side of the road.
Yes, okay, but it's not really a problem.
Good evening, Della, the principal.
Long in the eyes of the English teacher,
and you'll see the angel of death.
Breathe in your breath, and you'll discover hell.
Look between those five who fall,
and you'll know the city.
Thank you.
Why did you do that, Sophie?
I'm sure this door will be re-painted in the shortest time.
You can't re-paint this door.
Your daughter engraved her little poetry with her nails.
Then we'll have to change the door.
You have something to say to your English teacher?
Huh?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
What happened to you, Tondra?
Thank you.
Why are you so stressed out?
And I'm not stressed out?
It's a toilet door, sir!
Do you want people to go to hell or what?
Wait!
I speak loudly because you don't listen to me.
Yes.
Yes, very well.
Here, thank you, sir.
That's it. Everything's settled.
Huh?
How much do you want for the door?
Hmm.
Is it important?
My mum says you're wrong.
Well, it's nice of you to talk about me.
Your sister just went to sleep at home last night.
Ah.
She always takes it to her hiding place.
Can I sleep at your place?
Well...
Tonight...
You don't have to worry about me.
And when will it be possible?
Sophie, I...
Since divorce?
I've never come to your place. Not even once.
Are you sure?
Really? Don't tell me things like that.
Are you sure? You're always going to a Nazi cafΘ?
Like I was your mistress!
No, hey, stop it!
Huh?
I don't have the week of Louis' death.
You can't let it fall a bit.
Why do you call her Louise? Is she your mother?
The psychoanalyst's sessions have made it another day, okay?
She's going to miss me.
I know.
She's the only normal person in this family.
No, she's not quite normal.
I'm sure.
But she loves me.
Yes, you love her.
What do you draw?
Us.
I'm a goldsmith.
That's beautiful.
So, what do you want us to talk about?
I'll turn off the phone.
And there's a good lemon tart that hasn't arrived yet.
We're going to eat it all together.
I don't answer.
You and I,
we're part of the goldsmith.
I don't answer.
You and I,
we're part of the goldsmith.
This is a big loss.
I have to answer.
Yes, I'm with my accountant.
I remember.
What's this duty?
You're drunk.
And we're not alone.
You're alone?
Can you get up?
What?
No.
I can't move.
Move?
No.
No, no, no.
No, no, I'm coming. Don't move, don't move!
I have to go. I'll take you on your way.
What's going on?
There's a train passing by.
First of all, you.
What's that smell?
Petrol?
It's calva.
It's Richard's sister who did it herself.
What's happened to your arm?
Nothing.
Where's the can I gave you?
I lost it.
Already? Where is it?
It's Richard at the poker.
You played your can at the poker?
I had the hand of the dead.
The one of Wabbley and Cock.
Two aces of Anne.
A winning hand.
You lost your can with a winning hand.
Yes, and Robert had an umbrella then.
I'll take you there.
No, no, no. I'm fine here.
It's not possible. I don't want to leave you alone like that.
And you're not going to tell me what I have to do and not do?
But I want to help you.
You want to help me?
Good morning, club.
As the proverb says, it's easier to break than to stick.
I'm strong when it comes to breaking.
Sometimes to stick.
I'm happy to have your knowledge.
Olivier Tronnier.
Simon Helmallet.
You have glue.
Yes.
He's still late.
Who?
The big one.
It's your friend, that's good.
He's going to talk to you.
Philippe, yes.
We were very close friends.
We were.
Did something happen?
He gives you money too.
Why do you say that?
Just like that. I guessed.
You can call to check that he's well on the road.
He doesn't take my calls, he blocks me.
He's dead.
Ok, listen.
If there's one thing that I'm testing more than the money,
it's the breadwinners.
Tell Philippe that before 10,000 euros,
we're going to get 5,000 euros.
If he doesn't make this money in a second,
the amount goes to 7,000.
He died in an accident yesterday.
Of course.
He could have died.
A heart attack like everyone else.
5,000 euros until Friday.
Then it's 7,000.
If I were you, I'd take notes.
To avoid confusion.
But...
No, please.
It's an affair between Philippe and me.
Don't insist on that.
Excuse me, Mr Helmallet.
Shit.
Excuse me.
I have a question about...
about everything else.
You're in the car, aren't you?
Philippe talked to me about you yesterday.
Before or after his death?
I inherited from an immobile,
from General Brunet.
27, after General Brunet?
He talked to me, right?
Yes.
It's been a while since the immobile looks like that.
When Philippe was present in this affair, he told me.
He represented me, yes.
Of course, I forgot.
I wanted to sell it.
As you can see, I'm also in the immobile,
but I mostly take care of an isolated apartment.
Less projects on a large scale.
So, in relation to an animal like that...
What is it?
If you give it to me without a municipal tax,
or with the order of demolition,
and without locating it,
I give it to you.
Isn't it cute?